(crickets chirping)
(sneaky music playing)
(lowered voice) All clear?
(lowered voice)
On my signal.
Go, go, go! We gotta
get out before Hayley --
Dad?
(normal voice) Hayley's home!
(switch clicks)
Hey, girl!
What's going on?
Nothing or whatever.
Wait a minute. Dad's wearing
his special eating pants,
and Mom's got Tupperware labeled
"Cheesecake Warehouse."
(gasps) You're going
to the Cheesecake Warehouse!
Ugh. Now I suppose everybody
has to listen to a thing.
Did you know
the Cheesecake Warehouse
makes $2 billion a year
while their employees
make minimum wage?
It's not fair!
Hayley, let me break this down
like the great Vanessa Williams
in "A Diva's Christmas Carol."
¶ Don't be so serious,
there must be some mistake ¶
¶ Am I delirious
or do you want a cheesecake? ¶
The Cheesecake Warehouse is
the leading cause of diabetes
in the state of Virginia.
(all groan)
Hayley, you're always
ranting --
"This isn't fair,
that isn't fair,
"children don't belong
in factories,
I shouldn't print out
all my e-mails."
(scoffs)
You're such a downer.
Being opinionated
doesn't make me a downer.
Tell 'em, Jeff.
Well...
I can't believe this.
I'm used to hearing it
from them, but...
It's not you. It's just...
You kinda have a frowny face,
which can put people off.
If you just did this...
That's what I'm --
Hayley's back.
It's just how I look,
okay?
Actually,
that's not true.
You were the happiest
little 6-year-old.
Remember
her beautiful smile?
I had to fight
the kidnappers away.
Seriously?
Is it really so hard
to believe?
I mean,
am I so horrible?
Is it that impossible
to be around me?
(tires screech, engine revs)
¶ We made a getaway
'cause Hayley's hard to take ¶
¶ Dad put the pedal down,
we're gonna eat a cheesecake ¶
¶¶
¶ Good morning, U.S.A. ¶
¶ I got a feelin' that
it's gonna be a wonderful day ¶
¶ The sun in the sky
has a smile on his face ¶
¶ And he's shinin' a salute
to the American race ¶
¶ Oh, boy, it's swell to say ¶
¶ Good -- ¶
¶ Good morning, U.S.A. ¶
Aah!
(crickets chirping)
Hey, babe,
what you doing?
Oh, why'd you get out
your paper facebook?
Look at this.
i-I'm smiling in every picture.
It's weird, but I don't
remember any of this.
I guess 'cause drugs.
"Happy Hayley"?
God, what happened to me?
I mean, my family's
avoiding me.
What if I drive you away?
Babe, that'll never happen.
I got nowhere else to go.
Oh, happy Hayley.
Those were the days.
Oh, my God!
How are you doing that?
I'm from outer space, Jeff.
I can do lots of cool shit.
Here's a little sump'n sump'n
I learned on Vega Five.
(groans)
You remember happy Hayley?
What? Oh, sure.
Always smiling.
(baby voice)
You were a bunny-wunny.
You were a sweetie-cutie-
baby-honey-pie.
You were tooshy-wooshy-
boohjy-boohjy.
(normal voice) And now
I'm indifferent to you.
Oh, I wish I could remember
what it felt like
to be that happy.
You can.
Make an appointment
to see Dr. Penguin
for hypnotherapy.
Roger, I don't want you
messing around with my head.
Happy Hayley
at the petting zoo?!
Oh, I just
wanna love her forever!
Is Dr. Penguin
available now?
We can probably
squeeze you in,
but we don't take
insurance.
We don't know how.
(school bell rings)
So we're at
the cheesecake warehouse,
and Charlotte comes over.
We're in her section.
Nice.
And I said, "Charlotte,
I want you to take away
"this fork and knife
and bring me some pork
I can eat with a spoon."
(chuckles) She laughs
and probably forgets
about her blind son
for a moment.
But when the pork comes,
oh, my God.
What is it, Steve?
It was stringy,
tough, chewy even.
I had to ask for
my knife and fork back.
(all gasp)
Charlotte had to do
the walk of shame
to the utensil station,
and I went home
with a gut full of hard pork.
(lowered voice) Yo,
couldn't help but overhear.
You boys in the market
for some soft pork?
Oh, dear.
You want the perfect pork?
You gotta get yourself
a slow cooker.
Get outta here, tim.
You're not even
a real pervert.
A slow cooker really
makes that much of a difference?
After you do a slow cook,
you'll never look at pork
the same way again.
Whoa! Message received,
buddy.
Before I give you this,
there's one thing to remember.
The slower the cook,
the better the taste.
The slower the cook...
(whispers)
The better the taste.
(all gasp)
That guy's so weird
about pork.
Anyway...
(deep voice) I'm Batman.
(birds chirping)
So here's how it works.
I do hypnotherapy to help
people better themselves,
to stop smoking...
or start smoking.
I do both,
whichever's easier.
One's way easier.
Anyhow, we'll use hypnotherapy
to bring you back
to when you were 6,
and we'll find out
what made you so happy.
You're 6 years old again.
6 years old.
With every swing
of the watch,
you go a little deeper.
Happy Hayley.
Hayley's still in there
with Dr. Penguin?
How long has it been?
I don't know, Mr. S.
Hayley usually keeps track
of how long I sit.
(door opens)
Roger! Snap out of it!
Oh, my God.
I think I did it.
I quit!
I quit not smoking!
I gotta get a ciggy!
Hayley,
are you all right?
(high-pitched childish voice)
Daddy! Can we get ice cream?
Pretty, pretty please?!
Yeah, sure, if you can
tell me how old you are.
Silly Daddy. I'm 6!
What?
Roger, what did you --
(joint cracks)
Uhh!
(strained voice)
My back! It's the L-5!
(groans) Must...get to...
Vicodin stash.
Horsey ride! (giggles)
(grunting)
Whoa! Ride 'em, girl!
(laughing)
Ah!
(slurring) This was supposed
to be a fun night. (cries)
(birds chirping)
One, two, three...
Roger, we can't have
a grown woman
acting like a child.
This ain't
no Disney Channel.
...9, 10!
Couch attack!
Uhh!
Roger,
hypnotize Hayley back.
Okay, okay, just let me finish
this last one.
(inhales deeply)
(gulps)
Smoking's so glamorous.
(lighter clicks)
You're not 6 anymore.
Tag! You're it!
(giggling)
There's fishy! Fishy!
Oh, no. Happy Hayley,
my mortal enemy.
The monster is back.
Hurricane fishy!
Ugh. This is my fault
for not putting up
sandbags.
(birds chirping)
Mommy, I'm hungry.
Can I have a hot dog?
You want a hot dog?
And some
mint chip ice cream.
Why, uh, of course, honey.
I'll whip that up right now.
You're the best mommy
ever!
Hey!
This is my chance
to raise her right.
(inhales) Get her
into child acting...
(exhaling deeply)
Make some cash.
Daddy's home!
Look, Daddy, I made you
a friendship bracelet.
It means we're BFFs --
best friends forever.
But you can't ever take it off,
or else I'll know.
'Kay, promise you'll
never take it off?
I promise. I've been meaning
to get rid of my old one.
(gasps) He promised
he'd never take it off!
(voice breaking)
You're supposed to wear them
until they fall off!
It's in the rules!
(crickets chirping)
So, babe, I'm just curious.
I'm not really sure how
you feel about us right now.
I love you.
You're my best friend.
Oh, that's so great
to hear.
I love you, too,
Hayles.
It's so awesome
you're a princess.
What's that, Anna?
There's a stinky, hairy ogre
in the room?
You and your pee-pee
are gross.
(ticks, dings)
All right!
The roast is finally done.
Eight hours without food.
It's like I'm a poor!
Wait. Remember what
the salesman said
four times in the alley?
The slower the cook,
the better the taste.
I say we double the time.
Or why stop there?
Let's double the double.
(moans)
(timer winds)
This pork isn't coming out
until it's absolutely perfect.
Well, I've always said
I'm not gonna come out
until I'm absolutely perfect.
(gasps)
Hey, guys, we need
to talk about Hayley.
Isn't she great?
Look, she made me this
sweet-ass friendship bracelet.
Oh, did you not get one?
Aw.
No, guys, this is bad!
My wife is 6!
Oh, children are more sexual
than we realize.
It was my work in that area
that cemented my tenure
at the University
of the Ozarks.
Go, Possums!
Don't be selfish, Jeff.
Hayley's finally happy
again.
She eats everything, and she
lets me dress her up
however I want.
Mommy, look!
I'm as pretty as you!
Almost.
Dr. Penguin, there's gotta
be something you can do.
All right. Let's commence
the un-hypnotizing.
It's a very delicate procedure.
I'll need total silence.
Snap out of it!
Patty-cake, Roger!
BOTH (chanting):
¶ My mother, your mother
lived across the street ¶
¶ 1-8-1-9 Blueberry Street ¶
¶ Every night
they have a fight ¶
¶ This is what they said
that night ¶
¶ Boys go to Jupiter,
get more stupider ¶
¶ Girls go to Mars
to be superstars ¶
¶ Rumble, tumble,
strawberry shake ¶
Freeze!
(both laugh)
Ah, childhood.
Such a sweet, sexual time.
Hey!
You didn't fix her.
Sorry, Jeff, but Hayley
seems to be
in what is known as
age regression lock.
So she'll stay
a 6-year-old forever?
Not forever, but, yes,
until she dies.
That is, unless you find
her trigger.
Wait. What --
what do you mean?
Happy Hayley didn't stay
Happy Hayley.
(lighter clicks)
Something in her past
turned her
into the cranky, preachy
downer Hayley
that we all know
and you love.
Finding that trigger
should bring her back.
Enough
of this nonsense!
I think it's time
for a family trip
to the Cheesecake Warehouse!
Yay! Yay, yay, yay, yay!
Buffalo bites!
I'm in! I can smoke there
'cause it's gross.
Ugh. I need to find
Hayley's trigger.
I will help.
Yuck.
Klaus?
I've been hiding all week
from that 6-year-old asshole.
(birds chirping)
Whoa, look,
her 7th birthday party.
Oh, look how sad she is,
like a single baby's shoe
floating down the river.
Something at that party
made her stop smiling.
That was it!
That was the moment
she became downer Hayley!
What is she looking at?
There.
This boy behind Hayley
was taking a picture
at the same time.
If he still has it, then we
can see what Hayley saw.
Whoa, whoa,
one step at at time.
First, we have to go
through this whole yearbook
to try and find --
Oh, here he is. Joe chandler.
He has a camera
in his school picture, too.
Hmm. Bit of
a shutterbug, I suppose.
Great detective work,
Klaus.
Hey, we make
a pretty good team.
Looks like this case
was made for...
Fish and the Jeffman.
(both humming
"Wheels and the Legman" theme)
(humming continues)
(brakes squeal)
Damn it! Roger's suing us
for copyright infringement.
He says this is like
"Wheels and the Legman."
What?! In what way?!
(bubbling)
What are you boys doing?
It's been a week, Steve.
The meat's falling
off the bone!
The bone! All that flavor
trapped in the bone.
But what if we cook
the bone down to a jelly
and then the jelly down
to a broth,
and then the broth
down to a reduction?!
You're playing God with pork!
Just let us eat!
I knew you guys couldn't handle
the pressure of a slow cook.
Luckily, I'm ready.
Looks like you boys
brought hands
to a crossbow fight.
But I want food now!
Barry, tide yourself over
with a --
Don't you say it, Steve!
Don't you dare tell me
to eat another
Nature's Harvest bar!
I can't. My poops.
(crying)
They're like drywall.
You're asking if I have
a photo
I took at
a birthday party
that I went to
when I was 7?
We know it's a long shot,
Mr. Chandler,
but my wife's life
depends on it.
Oh, yeah.
I remember her.
I can't make any promises,
but I'll go have a look.
How am I supposed to find
one picture...
From the thousands and thousands
I've taken of her?
Thank God I digitized them all.
Joe Chandler,
you perfectly sane genius.
There it is.
(mouse clicks)
(printer whirring)
Boop. And one for me.
(mouse clicks,
printer whirring)
Mmm. Mmm...mmm.
Well, looks like
we're in luck.
I found the picture.
Oh, that's amazing!
Thanks, Joe.
Now, would I be imposing
if I asked you
to put a camera
in your pee hole?
What?
Boop.
Klaus, look.
Look where she's pointing.
Oh, a big man clubbing
a baby seal?
That is not fair.
That's it, Klaus!
This is the moment she realized
life wasn't fair.
That's her trigger.
Then we need
to recreate it.
That will snap her out
of the deep trance.
Let's go.
KLAUS: That Joe Chandler was
a cool dude.
Next time...
Next time I'll have bullets.
(crickets chirping)
(lowered voice) Jeff,
I love the symmetry of this.
Seeing a seal clubbed
to death
is what broke happy Hayley
the first time,
and doing it again
will break her once more.
Klaus, we're not gonna
club a seal to death.
You're right. It doesn't
have to be a seal.
Just anything innocent.
The important thing
is the club...and the death.
No, 'cause that's what turned
her into frowny-faced Hayley.
If we can just show her that
the world is unfair to animals
without murdering one, then
maybe she'll snap out of it,
but keep a little bit
of happy Hayley inside.
Oh, sucks.
I thought we were
on the same page
the whole drive.
Why are we
at the fish zoo?
Oh, just for fun.
Hey, look at
the pretty seals!
Wait a minute.
That's an awfully small place
for a seal to live.
It's not fair.
Right, Klaus?
Oh, yeah.
Look at these poor,
sweet, gentle creatures.
The lambs of the sea,
stuck their whole lives
in a tiny...
There's one behind me,
isn't there?
And is it, like,
exactly the opposite
of how I described them?
(growls)
Aah!
Klaus!
Aah! Help me!
Hold on!
Ohh! (panting)
In your face, seal.
You can't get me.
(growls)
Aah!
Seals can come on land?
I thought they had to stay
in the water like fish!
Oh, no. (gasps)
Evolve, Klaus. (gasps)
Evolve like the wind!
(grunts) Ow! Aah!
(growls)
Hey! (grunts)
(growling)
(barking)
Stay...away...from Klaus!
(panting)
Ooh! You killed it.
I want a mermaid key chain!
Oh, good, she didn't see me
kill the seal.
(click)
But we did.
(timer dings)
We did it, friends.
We cooked the perfect pork.
Wish you could try it,
but you're all dead.
(screaming)
(gasps) Oh, God!
The meaning of the dream
is so clear!
I gotta share this pork
with my friends immediately!
Oh, come on. Every morning?
Didn't you hear me?
There's no time. I need
to do the right thing
for my friends.
You should be
in that slow cooker, you pig.
(remote control clicks)
I know that's hard
to watch.
That's why I only showed it
to you 10 times.
Jeff Fischer broke
into the aquarium
and brutally killed a seal,
but not just any seal.
This was Harpy...
(remote control clicks)
...the cutest seal.
JURY: Aw.
I can't hear you!
JURY (louder): Aw!
The prosecution rests,
but not before a quick round
of high five
with this awesome jury!
(cheers and applause,
upbeat theme music playing)
What's happening, daddy?
That man is on trial because
he did a bad thing to a seal.
I like seals.
I don't like that man.
No one does.
(gavel bangs)
So, does the defendant
want to waste our time
before the jury
finds him guilty?
We'd like to call
Dr. Penguin to the stand.
Huh?
Who's Dr. Penguin?
That'd be me.
I can explain why Jeff
did what he did,
or if I may hypnotize
the jury, your honor?
Oh, fun! I'll allow it.
Jeff Fischer is not guilty.
Not guilty. With every swing
of the watch,
you'll find Jeff
a little less guilty.
We find the defendant
not guilty.
Okay, cool.
Jeff Fischer, you're free to go.
(gavel bangs)
Yes!
(gallery shouting at once)
Daddy, what's wrong?
The man who killed the seal
is being let go.
What?! But that's not fair!
That's not fair.
(gruff voice) That's not fair.
(clears throat)
(normal voice)
That's not fair.
Oh. Whoa.
Where the hell am I?
Ugh. Hayley's back.
Hayley! I've missed you
so much.
Missed me?
But where have I been?
The real question is
when have you been?
(laughter)
Seriously, guys, I can't account
for a lot of time,
and I'm kind of freaking out.
Will someone please explain
what's happening?
More like, who's happening,
right, guys?
(laughter)
(crickets chirping)
Guys, I'm sorry I got
carried away
with the slow cooker,
but my pursuit of perfection
was not totally in vain,
'cause like the pork,
our friendship has been
simmered to perfection.
Let's eat!
Mmm. Mmm.
Divine.
Yet it leaves
something behind.
Metallic, maybe?
Furry.
Almost moving?
With perhaps
maggoty undertones?
(siren wailing)
Who gave you
the stupid idea
you could eat
12-day-old pork?
He did!
(snorting)
He's pigs! He's pigs!
(grunts)
I gotta restrain this one.
He's on to us.
This isn't an ambulance!
It's a goddamn hambulance!
(snorting alarm wailing)
(gasping)
Pigs. Pigs everywhere.
They're all pigs.
I think Steve ate
a lot more than us.
(grunting)
Thanks for looking out
for me, Jeff.
I'm glad to be back
to my old self,
even if happy Hayley
is gone for good.
It's all right, babe.
I love you no matter what.
Hey, wanna grab a bite
before the P.E.T.A. protest?
Sure. For some reason,
I could go for a scoop
of mint chip.
Hey! You're smiling, babe.
That's one for the scrapbook.
(camera shutter clicks,
whirs)
(whispers) I hate this part.
Bye! Have a beautiful time!
-- Captions by VITAC --