ANNOUNCER:
Feeling a little tired
of America's number-one sport,
football?
God, they're pathetic!
There's got to be a better way.
And there already is.
Arena football!
Unforgiving sideline barriers!
(bones crack,
cheers and applause)
Water cannons!
(bones crack)
(screams)
And you better
watch out for...
the Black Knight!
It's arena football.
And the indoor thrills
are coming your way
as the league welcomes
its newest expansion team --
the Langley Falls
Bazooka Sharks!
Finally! Yeah!
Yeah! Ah! Yeah!
Yeah!
Yeah! Yeah!
(all shouting)
¶ Good morning, U.S.A. ¶
¶ I got a feelin' that
it's gonna be a wonderful day ¶
¶ The sun in the sky
has a smile on his face ¶
¶ And he's shinin' a salute
to the American race ¶
¶ Oh, boy, it's swell to say ¶
¶ Good -- ¶
¶ Good morning, U.S.A. ¶
Aah!
Old Man Hansen, do you sell
Bazooka Sharks merchandise?
I'm looking for one of those
Snuggies with a built-in diaper
and a place I can put
my driver's license.
That blasted
arena football team!
We've been here
three generations,
and now they're tearing us down
to put in the new stadium.
You poor old man.
This lamp sucks.
I'll give you 2 bucks for it.
Mom!
That is disgusting.
Taking advantage of -- Wait.
Half off this bird cage?
Please,
I could really use this.
I foster abused birds.
I'd like to
put a candle in it.
I still have one shot
to save the store.
There's a town council meeting
about the stadium tonight.
Tonight, eh?
Oh, I'll be there.
Please don't come if you're
gonna support the stadium.
It's too late.
What's to become of you with
the store closing, Petruchio?
It could-a be time to find
the guy who killed my brother.
Mm, now,
what is this lining?
Is a fine Bemberg lining,
Mr. Steve.
Bemberg, not silk.
Well, you've been right about
this kind of thing before.
Snot went nuts for me
in paisley.
Inseam always-a 20 inches.
I-Is that unusual?
You see, all the other boys --
bum, bum, bum,
they are growing.
You -- bum, bum, bum.
You hear the difference?
They go on
to men's-a department.
But you stay
with Petruchio.
Y-You're telling me
I'm not growing at all?
Not in two years.
And it says it's been-a
three days since-a you poop.
Let me see that book.
A-never.
I am not growing!
Look!
Nothing's happening!
Yeah, when we flew to Hawaii
last summer,
you sat on Dad's lap
for free.
I haven't grown in years.
And it's actually
quite liberating.
Gives me time to focus
on all my other shit.
B-B-But what if I
never grow again?
Look, if you really
want to do something,
I know a doctor who specializes
in growth treatments.
A specialist --
that's where the money is.
I should probably talk
to my dad about this.
Steve,
you want to talk?
Oh, yeah.
I wanted to ask you --
There's no time.
Your mother and I
have to hurry
down to the town
council meeting.
I hope
they let me speak.
I didn't put my name on a list
or anything.
Of course they'll let you,
honey. You're tall.
You're right.
I'm to be taken seriously.
Oh, Steve,
that really ties into
what you were talking about
earlier.
BUCKLE: The sign outside
needs to be updated.
And I say
we just break the glass
instead of continuing
this preposterous 30-year search
for the key.
And I say the key
is still out there.
Agreed.
We'll now hear the last
of the community objections
to the arena football stadium.
First up is Old Man Hansen.
(clears throat)
Good people of Langley Falls,
I ask you to join me
in standing up to the no-good
crooks on our city council.
These bums are lining their
pockets with their dirty deals,
and they need to be hogtied
and thrown down a well!
(clears throat)
Sorry.
I'm a little nervous.
You're doing great.
It's important
for Langley Falls
to protect
our historic places.
Also, while I'm up here,
my name isn't Old Man Hansen.
It's Olmen -- Olmen Hansen.
It's Swedish. I'm 43.
I think we've all heard just
about enough from Old Man H.
He doesn't know
what he's talking about.
If you don't count
our two hockey teams
and our championship
basketball squad --
Go, Lizards -- we have no
indoor sports in this town.
We need indoor sports
for the times when it's raining!
Look at this beautiful vision
of the future.
It's time for us to join the
ranks of the other great cities
in the Arena League
Mid-Atlantic Conference.
I'm talking Wilkes-Barre,
Harrisburg, Wilmington.
[Bleep] Wilmington!
Great cities
have to move forward.
And you know what else
has to move forward?
Uh, parades?
Sharks.
Bazooka sharks.
Wow.
Parades isn't wrong.
We can't go back to the past.
We can't go back to
a time before arena football.
No go back!
ALL:
(chanting "No go back")
Wait, what is this?
COUNCILMAN #2: Oh, just some
tree that's gonna be cut down
to make way
for the arena.
I'd like to go back on
my previous statement.
(all gasp)
But no go back.
This stadium cannot happen.
Mr. Smith,
you've made a passionate case
in favor of progress,
and now, before us and God
and the Langley charter,
you mysteriously
reverse your position?
You are, simply put, the most
electric speaker I've ever seen.
I-I just think
we're, uh, rushing into things.
That's what I'm saying.
Can someone put Grandpa to bed?
I'm trying to talk here.
We went to high school
together!
Let's get real, you guys.
Do we even want this stadium?
Arena football
is kind of lame.
(all gasp)
Mr. Smith,
what is really going on here?
It obviously has something to do
with that tree.
Now, come on.
You can talk to us.
We're your town council.
We love you.
(sighs) All right.
If you must know, that tree...
that tree is my father.
What does that
even mean?
It means he's half tree.
Question is,
what's the other half?
(indistinct shouting)
Order, order.
Stenographer, can you read
those last parts back?
And then Mr. Smith said,
"That tree is my father,"
at which point, the stenographer
blacked out from excitement
and the record stops.
I apologize to the council.
I ate some almonds.
I'm good now.
Mr. Smith, I think we're ready
to hear what you mean
when you say
this tree is your father.
Okay.
I'll tell you.
(chairs creak)
I was just a little --
I was just --
(chair creaks)
Is everyone comfortable?
I was just a little kid.
The father-son picnic.
And, as usual, my dad, Jack, was
the only one who didn't show up.
I felt so alone.
But then -- then I wasn't.
After that, I came back
every day after school.
I know this sounds crazy,
but the tree raised me.
He taught me how to play catch.
He watched me grow.
He helped me start
my first business,
even gave me my product.
Turns out magnolia juice is
as poisonous as it is delicious.
And no matter what,
he kept me safe.
His mighty roots connected me
to something constant,
something I could depend on,
when so often life is cruel
and unreliable.
He has been and always will be
there for me.
Please don't kill
my tree daddy.
My God, Stan.
How come I've never heard of
this tree father before?
I've brought you there
tons of time.
I made us have our wedding
there.
Oh. I just thought
you were a cheap asshole.
In light of new facts
and emotions,
I move to cancel
the stadium construction.
All in favor?
ALL: Aye.
All opposed?
(all gasp)
It's Dom Fikowski,
the asphalt king.
He runs asphalt
in this town.
Don't you think
I know that?
Y'all know me.
Y'all know what I do.
I sling the hot stuff, the flat
makings, the stone carpet.
I'm sure you folks are hearing a
lot of objections to the arena.
Taxes, traffic, crime --
so much crime.
Crime is a problem.
Think of the advantages
from an asphalt-pouring
standpoint.
With the new parking lots alone,
we're looking at two square
miles of sizzling-hot tarmac.
When the sun starts beating
on it,
the average temperature around
town is gonna go up 10 degrees.
With all the balmy,
roasting breezes,
it's gonna feel like
we're on permanent vacation.
ALL: Ooh.
And if you're still
on the fence,
allow me to get you off...
the fence
with some free asphalt.
Aw!
(laughs) It burns.
The stadium is back on.
(gavel bangs)
Roger,
you can't build the stadium.
You're standing here
in a parking lot I poured,
asking me
not to pour asphalt?
Pouring asphalt is what I do,
Stan.
If you do this, it would mean
the death of my dad tree.
Ugh.
I really wanted this pour.
But out of respect
for our friendship,
I'll withdraw my bid, kill the
project, and save your tree.
We did it, Tree Dad.
They're not gonna cut you down.
And it's all thanks
to Roger.
That paper boy
always finds me.
PAPER BOY: It's 'cause
I'm in love with you.
"Stadium off...
to the races."
What?
"Carconi Brothers
pick up construction bid
after Fikowski drops out."
Carconi Brothers.
I knew it would be you.
You have to cancel this project.
You promised.
But I don't control anything
around here.
I'm just
dumb old Frankie.
My twin brother, Freddie's,
the boss, and what he says goes.
I screw up a lot.
Stupid Frankie.
So, your twin brother
is who I have to talk to?
So tedious.
FREDDIE:
Damn it, Frankie!
You just let some nut come in
and open my plywood door?
He was so fast, Freddie.
You have a human brother?
Oh, yeah.
And Mama just loves Freddie.
She lets him have sex
with girls
but puts my ear to the stove
for playing with the chickens.
How's that figure,
you stupid mama?
(gasps)
I'm sorry, Mama.
(smooching)
I-I-I can't get into this
right now.
You can't tear down
my tree father.
I can't stop it.
I'm drowning
in bulldozer invoices.
I'm supposed to
keep the yellow copy,
but the purple one's prettier.
What can I do for you today,
little buddy?
You want to do something
about that skin?
I'm here because it's come to my
attention that I am not growing.
(laughs) You want to know
the secret to growing?
Get lots of sleep,
eat lots of veggies,
and always remember
your inner worth,
'cause that'll make you feel
10 feet tall.
Oh.
Klaus made it sound like
you might have more
immediate solutions.
You know Klaus?
(German accent)
That changes everything.
Much can be done
about your height.
Are you familiar with
the abominable sciences?
There's bone splicing,
giraffe marrow transplant.
I could boil your brain
in gorilla hormones.
I also have
unorthodox options.
For instance,
I could have your soul
put into the body
of something taller.
How comfortable are you
with the serpent god Oxumaré?
Not super comfortable.
We'll stick to surgery,
then!
I'd like to think on it.
What's there
to think about?
If B.B. King had come to me,
he would have never died...
at the height he was.
The Carconi Brothers are
coming to tear you down.
They're coming,
and -- and I don't have any
ideas about how to stop them.
(engines rumble)
Get out of the way,
you tree-hugging fruit.
So,
you think I'm a fruit, huh?
Well, then a fruit
I shall become.
Oh, my God, Freddie,
we can't chop down a tree
with a homosexual man
in it.
Ugh, no.
I made a gay slur,
then he threw it back in my face
by acting like the kind of fruit
that grows on trees.
Everybody thinks so fast.
Stan Smith, remove yourself
from the tree immediately.
Not until you promise
you won't cut it down.
That's a great idea.
I'll go and get on the roof
of my store right --
I'm so sorry.
Can I offer you
a temporary tattoo?
I'll get him down,
Freddie.
I know just how
to play this guy.
Please get down.
Freddie says
the budget's so tight
that if you delay us
just seven days,
the whole thing'll be canceled,
saving your stupid tree.
Seven days?
I can do that
for my tree dad.
(gasps)
Dumb Frankie.
Dumb. Dumb.
W-What are you, uh --
W-What do you get
out of this Frankie thing?
Actually, I get some great intel
for Fikowski Asphalt.
It's me, Dom Fikowski.
You'll never make it
a week.
¶¶
(wind whistles)
(all shouting)
(thunder cracks)
Dr. Kalgary, I've decided I --
Oh, you're with a patient.
It's just Billy.
He's part of the program.
One of my success stories.
I used to be
six inches tall.
Now
I'm Daddy's favorite.
Look at me walk.
Oh, my God.
W-Well, despite...this,
I still want the operation.
I need to grow.
Wonderful!
You'll be able to look over
any stall in the men's room
and see what's happening.
Hooray.
It's coming to the end of day 7
in --
Oop, that weird Carconi brother
who's always telling everyone
he's an honorary firefighter
is approaching the tree now.
Well, Freddie says
once the sun sets,
we got to send
the crew home.
That means
the stadium's dead
and he's not gonna take me
to Mountain Mike's Pizza.
(voice breaking)
And it's the sauciest pizza.
Oh,
my sweet flesh family.
Come, be with me
in my hour of triumph.
Honey,
you've blown me away
with your commitment
to this hunger strike.
It wasn't supposed to be
a hunger strike.
I kept asking you
to bring me food.
But I stood strong.
Hayley, who would have thought
that between the two of us,
I'd be the first one
to save a tree?
I've saved lots of trees.
I'm sorry.
You're right, sweetie.
Not ever buying or reading books
is also a way of saving trees.
Where's Steve?
Yeah, where is Steve?
Oh, you guys don't know?
Steve's with my associate,
Dr. Kalgary,
about to undergo
an irreversible,
fabulously risky,
height-boosting procedure.
What?
Steve will be sliced
into pieces,
and when he's reassembled,
he'll be exactly like the boy
you remember,
only taller
and with a lot more bones...
if he lives.
Oh, God.
Why would Steve do something
like this?
Wait, does he think
he stopped growing?
Yeah, that's right.
I know
what this is about.
You do?
Yep.
Well?
It's sounds like he could
use some guidance, Stan.
I agree.
But for whatever reason,
he never developed
a relationship with a tree.
Poor kid.
I think
you can be his tree.
A human tree father.
It sounds so stupid.
But to hell with how it sounds.
Steve needs me.
But if I leave to save him,
they're gonna cut you down.
(wind whistles)
You're right.
Steve's my responsibility now.
You're still teaching me.
I guess...this is goodbye.
I love you, Tree Daddy.
He's gone!
(singsong voice)
Frankie gets the pizza.
(sobs)
¶ The surgeon
cuts at night ¶
¶ I'm gonna cut you,
Steve ¶
¶ I'm gonna cut you right ¶
Actually, uh, you know,
I think I've changed my mi--
Oh.
They always get cold feet.
And I always
cut them off.
Aah!
STEVE: Oh, my God.
I'm so tall.
It's gonna take
some getting used to.
Aaaaah!
Aaaaaah!
Look out, Steve.
I made things worse for you.
Hold on, son.
I can climb up.
(voice breaking)
Someone taught me how.
Dad, get it together!
Coming.
(saw whirring)
(metal creaking)
Aaaah!
You're here.
Of course I am.
It's what dads do.
Even when their kid's
a stupid shorty?
Steve, there's something
I have to show you.
(siren wailing)
(gasps) The fuzz!
Time to see if your wings work,
Billy!
Run, Billy!
When I was a boy,
I used to carve my height
here on the bark.
This extra-deep one
is from a few years
where I didn't grow at all.
It's called
the Smith Stall.
But eventually,
I shot up six inches.
So I will get tall.
But even if I didn't,
it doesn't matter
because I have a dad
who loves me.
You're gonna get tall.
So, this tree w-was like a dad
to you or something?
I know.
We'll both miss him.
But he goes on now
to a greater purpose.
May his timber bring shelter
to a deserving soul.
Please don't cut down this tree.
It's like a father to me.
The world...needs
...ax handles.
Bye! Have a beautiful time!